Guide to the Office of Fraternity and Sorority Life records, 1964-2012 UA.09.12.0002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession UA2013-0026, 1964-2011
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: Board of Advisors: Members, 1996-1997 (Box 11)
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: Board of Advisors: Alcohol Policy, 1997 (Box 11)
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: Board of Advisors: Unfoldered 69, circa 1997 (Box 11)
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: Board of Directors, 1995-1997 (Box 11)
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: Board of Directors: Alcohol Policies, 1994-1997 (Box 11)
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: Board of Directors: Unfoldered 70, 1992-1995 (Box 11)
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: North American Interfraternity Conference (NIC), 2002 August-November (Box 11)
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled AD: Annual Report, 1992-1993 (Box 12)
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled AD: Board of Advisors Meeting, 1996 (Box 12)
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled AD: Board of Advisors Meeting, 1995 (Box 12)
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled AD: Board of Advisors Meeting, 1995 (Box 12)
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled AD: Untitled 15, 1996-2000 (Box 12)
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled AD: Untitled 16, 1996-1999 (Box 12)
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: Emergency Response, 2008-2009 (Box 12)
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: EBI Survey, 2008 October-December (Box 12)
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled AE: Halloween Carnival, 2005-2008 (Box 12)
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled AE: Service and Philanthropy Habitat, 2007 September-November (Box 12)
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled AE: Greek Women's Leadership Dinner Series, 2008 October-November (Box 12)
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled AE: Council Executive Retreat, 2007 (Box 12)
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: Untitled 17, 1997-2003 (Box 12)
  - Old Interfraternity Council Files: Order of Omega, 2003-2004 (Box 12)
  - Clarybel Files NPHC/Early Matriculation: National Pan-Hellenic Council: DABGLO, 1994-1995 (Box 12)
  - Clarybel Files NPHC/Early Matriculation: National Pan-Hellenic Council, 1996-1999 (Box 12)
  - Clarybel Files NPHC/Early Matriculation: National Pan-Hellenic Council: Unfoldered 71, 1998-1999 (Box 12)
  - Clarybel Files NPHC/Early Matriculation: National Pan-Hellenic Council:, 1995-1997 (Box 12)
  - Clarybel Files NPHC/Early Matriculation: National Pan-Hellenic Council: North Carolina Central University University Membership Intake Procedures, 1999 February-March (Box 12)
  - Clarybel Files NPHC/Early Matriculation: National Pan-Hellenic Council:, 1996-1998 (Box 12)
  - Clarybel Files NPHC/Early Matriculation: National Pan-Hellenic Council: DABGLO, 1992-1994 (Box 12)
  - Clarybel Files NPHC/Early Matriculation: Untitled AF: Unfoldered 72, 2000-2001 (Box 12)
  - Clarybel Files NPHC: Untitled AF: Early Matriculation, 2000-2001 (Box 12)
  - Clarybel Files NPHC/Early Matriculation: Untitled AF: Untitled 18, 2001 (Box 12)
  - Clarybel Files NPHC/Early Matriculation: Untitled AF: Orientation, 2001-2005 (Box 12)
  - Clarybel Files NPHC: Early Matriculation Materials: Program Room Assignment, 2001 June-August (Box 12)
  - Clarybel Files NPHC: Early Matriculation Program: Unfoldered 73, 2000 (Box 12)
  - Clarybel Files NPHC: Early Matriculation: Unfoldered 74, 2000 (Box 12)
  - Clarybel Files NPHC: Early Matriculation: Residential Summer Camp Counselor, 2000 (Box 12)
  - Clarybel Files NPHC: Early Matriculation: Summer Mailings, 2000 May-June (Box 12)
  - Clarybel Files NPHC: Early Matriculation: Budget Information, 2000 May-June (Box 12)
  - Clarybel Files NPHC/Early Matriculation: Untitled 19, 2000-2001 (Box 12)
  - Clarybel Files NPHC/Early Matriculation: Untitled 20, 2000-2001 (Box 12)
  - Clarybel Files NPHC: Early Matriculation Program: Untitled 21, 2000-2001 (Box 12)
  - Clarybel Files NPHC: Early Matriculation Program: Untitled 22, 2000-2001 (Box 12)
  - Clarybel Files NPHC/Early Matriculation: Unfoldered 75, 2001 (Box 12)
  - Clarybel Files NPHC/Early Matriculation: Intake Requirement, 2000 (Box 12)
  - Clarybel Files NPHC/Early Matriculation: Pan-Hellenic Council, 1999-2002 (Box 12)
  - Clarybel Files NPHC/Early Matriculation: Phi Beta Sigma Alpha Alpha Chi, 1993-2000 (Box 12)
  - Clarybel Files NPHC/Early Matriculation: Untitled 23, 2000-2001 (Box 12)
  - Clarybel Files NPHC/Early Matriculation: Unfoldered 76, 2000 (Box 12)
  - Interfraternity Council Active Files: Greek Relationship Statements: Unfoldered 77, 2005 (Box 12)
  - Interfraternity Council Active Files: Greek Relationship Statements: CAS Standards, 2006 (Box 12)
  - Interfraternity Council Active Files: Greek Relationship Statements: University of Rochester, 2003 (Box 12)
  - Interfraternity Council Active Files: Greek Relationship Statements: Call for Values Congruence, 1999-2005 (Box 13)
  - Interfraternity Council Active Files: Greek Relationship Statements: Creating Chapters of Excellence, 2004-2005 (Box 13)
  - Interfraternity Council Active Files: Greek Relationship Statements: Miami University, 1996 October-June
  - Interfraternity Council Active Files: Greek Relationship Statements: Albion College, 2003 (Box 13)
  - Interfraternity Council Active Files: Untitled AG: Assessment, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Interfraternity Council Active Files: Untitled AG: EBI/AFA, 2004 (Box 13)
  - Interfraternity Council Active Files: Untitled AH: The Ohio State, 2000-2006 (Box 13)
  - Interfraternity Council Active Files: Untitled AH: University of Florida, 2005 (Box 13)
  - Interfraternity Council Active Files: Untitled AH: Cornell, 2005 (Box 13)
  - Interfraternity Council Active Files: Untitled AH: Creating Chapters of Excellence, 2005 (Box 13)
  - Interfraternity Council Active Files: Fraternity Development Plans, Examples: Emory University, 1999 (Box 13)
  - Interfraternity Council Active Files: Fraternity Development Plans, Examples: Emory University Phoenix Plan Total Management of Greek Facilities, 1999 (Box 13)
  - Interfraternity Council Active Files: Fraternity Development Plans, Examples: Emory University, 2003 (Box 13)
  - Interfraternity Council Active Files: Fraternity Development Plans, Examples: Ron Kuhlman Ohio Northern Plan, circa 2003 (Box 13)
  - Interfraternity Council Active Files: Fraternity Development Plans, Examples: Louisiana State University, 2003 (Box 13)
  - Interfraternity Council Active Files: Fraternity Development Plans, Examples: Ohio University, 2003 (Box 13)
  - Interfraternity Council Active Files: Fraternity Development Plans, Examples: Georgia College & State University, 2003 (Box 13)
  - Interfraternity Council Active Files: Fraternity Development Plans, Examples: University of Nevada, Las Vegas, 1996 (Box 13)
  - Interfraternity Council Active Files: Fraternity Development Plans, Examples: University of Texas, San Antonio, 2003 (Box 13)
  - Interfraternity Council Active Files: Untitled AI: Ball State University, 1998 (Box 13)
  - Interfraternity Council Active Files: Untitled AI: University of California, Berkeley, circa 2000 (Box 13)
  - Interfraternity Council Active Files: Untitled AI: University of Toledo, 2002 (Box 13)
  - Interfraternity Council Active Files: Untitled AI: University of Virginia, 1998 (Box 13)
  - Interfraternity Council Active Files: Untitled AI: Southern Illinois Carbondale, 2002 (Box 13)
  - Interfraternity Council Active Files: Judi, Board Proceeding, 1999-2006 (Box 13)
  - Interfraternity Council Active Files: Oklahoma State University, circa 2001 (Box 13)
  - Interfraternity Council Active Files: NC State, circa 2001 (Box 13)
  - Interfraternity Council Active Files: University of Rochester, 2005 (Box 13)
  - Interfraternity Council Active Files: NC Central, 1997 (Box 13)
  - Interfraternity Council Active Files: University of Florida, circa 2001 (Box 13)
  - Interfraternity Council Active Files: Penn, 2002 (Box 13)
  - Clarybel Historical Files: Alpha Epsilon Pi, 1981-1997 (Box 13)
  - Clarybel Historical Files: Alpha Tau Omega, 1993-1999 (Box 13)
  - Clarybel Historical Files: Beta Theta Pi, 1993-1997 (Box 13)
  - Clarybel Historical Files: Kappa Alpha, 1993-1997 (Box 13)
  - Clarybel Historical Files: Kappa Sigma, 1987-1998 (Box 13)
  - Clarybel Historical Files: Delta Kappa Epsilon, 1989-1994 (Box 13)
  - Clarybel Historical Files: Delta Sigma Phi, 1986-1997 (Box 13)
  - Clarybel Historical Files: Delta Tau Delta (Inactive), 1982-1994 (Box 13)
  - Clarybel Historical Files: Omega Psi Phi, 1985 (Box 13)
  - Clarybel Historical Files: Alpha Phi Alpha, 1993-1997 (Box 13)
  - Clarybel Historical Files: Phi Delta Theta, 1983-1997 (Box 13)
  - Clarybel Historical Files: Phi Kappa Sigma (Inactive), 1993-1994 (Box 13)
  - Clarybel Historical Files: Phi Kappa Phi (Inactive), 1985 (Box 13)
  - Clarybel Historical Files: Psi Kappa Alpha, 1993-1997 (Box 13)
  - Clarybel Historical Files: Wayne Manor, 2000-2001 (Box 13)
  - Clarybel Historical Files: Wayne Manor: Living Groups, circa 2000 (Box 13)
  - Clarybel Historical Files: Wayne Manor: Living Groups Officer Lists, 1993-2002 (Box 13)
  - Clarybel Historical Files: Wayne Manor: Living Groups Correspondence General, 1982-2000 (Box 13)
  - Clarybel Historical Files: Wayne Manor: Living Groups Constitution, 1973-1997 (Box 13)
  - Clarybel Historical Files: Wayne Manor: Living Groups Damages, 1999-2002 (Box 13)
  - Clarybel Historical Files: Wayne Manor: Living Groups Sanction/Discipline, 2000-2002 (Box 13)
  - Clarybel Historical Files: Untitled AJ: Unfoldered 78, 2000-2003 (Box 13)
  - Clarybel Historical Files: Untitled AJ: Interfraternity Council, 2000-2003 (Box 13)
  - Clarybel Historical Files: Untitled AJ: Untitled 24, 1977-2000 (Box 13)
  - Clarybel Historical Files: Annual Reports: Unfoldered 79, 2003 (Box 13)
  - Clarybel Historical Files: Annual Reports: Unfoldered 80, 2003 (Box 13)
  - Clarybel Historical Files: Annual Reports: Unfoldered 81, 2003 (Box 13)
  - Clarybel Historical Files: Unfoldered 82, 2001 (Box 13)
  - Untitled A: Higher Education Center for Alcohol and Other Drug Prevention, 1999-2000 (Box 13)
  - Untitled A: Academic Support/Academic Resources, circa 2000 (Box 13)
  - Untitled A: Arbitration, circa 2000 (Box 13)
  - Untitled A: Campus Activities Magazine, 2001 January-October (Box 13)
  - Untitled A: Shoot for the Best, 2001 (Box 13)
  - Untitled A: Concepts and Connnections, 1996-2005 (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: Diversity, circa 2000 (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: FIPG, 1993-1997 (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: Fraternity Management Group, 1998-2003 (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: Todd's File Greek Research, 1990-2000 (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: Hazing: Unfoldered 83, 2000-2008 (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: Hazing: Broken Pledges The Deadly Rite of Hazing, 1996 (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: Hazing: Unfoldered 84, 1999-2002 (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: Hazing: Fall 2000: Hazing Meetings, 1998-2001 (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: Hazing: Hazing on Campus, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: Hazing: Unfoldered 85, circa 2000 (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: Hazing: Policy and Procedures Hazing, 1981-1989 (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: Greek Housing, 2002-2006 (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: Unfoldered 86, 2001-2003 (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: Untitled AK: FIPG, 2003 (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: Untitled AK: Unfoldered 87, 2000-2004 (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: Untitled AK: Unfoldered 88, 2000-2004 (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: Humor/Creativity, 1998 (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: NASPA Forum, 2001-2002 (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: Leadership, 1999-2002 (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: Articles on Residential Life, 1991-1993 (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: Scholarship, circa 1995 (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: Sophomore Leadership Class, 1999-2000 (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: Speaker/Consultant, 2003-2008 (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: Untitled AL: Unfoldered 89, 2003 (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: Untitled AL: Alcohol, 1997-2003 (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: Untitled AL: Crime-General, 1997-2001 (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: Untitled AL: Diversity, etc. Issues, 1999-2001 (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: Untitled AL: Miscellaneous Greek, 1996-1999 (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: Untitled AM: Positive Press, 1999 February-October (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: Untitled AM: Rush/Hazing, 1982-1999 (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: Untitled AM: Sexual Assault etc., 1987-1991 (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: Untitled AM: Sororities, 1999 June-November (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: Untitled AM: Strategic Planning, 2001-2005 (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: RGAC, circa 2004 (Box 14)
  - Untitled A: Newsletter, 2004-2006 (Box 14)
  - Annual Reports: Sample Constitutions: Living Groups, 1993-1999 (Box 14)
  - Annual Reports: Sample Constitutions: Living Groups, Security Vote Results, 1999 (Box 14)
  - Annual Reports: Correspondence: General: Annual Review, 1999-2004 (Box 14)
  - Annual Reports: Annual Review Correspondence: General: Unfoldered 90, 2003 (Box 14)
  - Annual Reports: Annual Review Correspondence: General: Fall Reports, Spring Letters, 2002-2003 (Box 14)
  - Annual Reports: Annual Review Correspondence: General: Unfoldered 91, 2001-2002 (Box 14)
  - Annual Reports: Correspondence: General: Annual Review, 2000-2001 (Box 14)
  - Annual Reports: Annual Review Correspondence: General: Living Groups, 1993-1994 (Box 14)
  - Annual Reports: Annual Review Correspondence: General: Unfoldered 92, 1997-2001 (Box 14)
  - Annual Reports: Alpha Epsilon Pi: Living Groups Annual Review Correspondence: General, 2002-2007 (Box 14)
  - Annual Reports: Alpha Phi Alpha: Living Groups Annual Review Correspondence: General, 2002-2003 (Box 15)
  - Annual Reports: Alpha Tau Omega: Living Groups Annual Review Correspondence: General, circa 2003 (Box 15)
  - Annual Reports: Alpha Tau Omega: Alpha Tau Omega, 2000-2001 (Box 15)
  - Annual Reports: Beta Theta Pi: Living Groups Annual Review Correspondence: General, 2002-2007 (Box 15)
  - Annual Reports: Beta Theta Pi: Beta Theta Pi, 2000-2001 (Box 15)
  - Annual Reports: Brownstone: Living Groups Annual Review Correspondence: General, 2002-2003 (Box 15)
  - Annual Reports: Cleland: Living Groups Annual Review Correspondence: General, 2002-2003 (Box 15)
  - Annual Reports: Decker: Living Groups Annual Review Correspondence: General, 2002-2003 (Box 15)
  - Annual Reports: Delta Kappa Epsilon: Living Groups Annual Review Correspondence: General, 1997-2007 (Box 15)
  - Annual Reports: Delta Sigma Phi: Living Groups Annual Review Correspondence: General, 2002-2007 (Box 15)
  - Annual Reports: Delta Tau Delta: Living Groups Annual Review Correspondence: General, 2006-2007 (Box 15)
  - Annual Reports: Kappa Alpha: Living Groups Annual Review Correspondence: General, 2002-2007 (Box 15)
  - Annual Reports: Kappa Sigma: Living Groups Annual Review Correspondence: General, 2002 February-April (Box 15)
  - Annual Reports: Maxwell: Living Groups Annual Review Correspondence: General, 2002-2003 (Box 15)
  - Annual Reports: Mirecourt: Living Groups Annual Review Correspondence: General, 2002-2003 (Box 15)
  - Annual Reports: Mitchell (Arts): Living Groups Annual Review Correspondence: General, 2002-2003 (Box 15)
  - Annual Reports: Phi Delta Theta: Living Groups Annual Review Correspondence: General, 2002-2007 (Box 15)
  - Annual Reports: Phi Kappa Psi: Spring, 2000-2001 (Box 15)
  - Annual Reports: Pi Kappa Alpha: Living Groups Annual Review Correspondence: General, 2002-2007 (Box 15)
  - Annual Reports: Pi Kappa Phi, 2006-2007 (Box 15)
  - Annual Reports: PRISM: Living Groups Annual Review Correspondence: General, 2002-2003 (Box 15)
  - Annual Reports: Psi Upsilon: Living Groups Annual Review Correspondence: General, 2002-2007 (Box 15)
  - Annual Reports: Round Table: Living Groups Annual Review Correspondence: General, 2002-2004 (Box 15)
  - Annual Reports: Scott: Living Groups Annual Review Correspondence: General, 2002-2003 (Box 15)
  - Annual Reports: Share: Living Groups Annual Review Correspondence: General, 2002-2003 (Box 15)
  - Annual Reports: Sigma Alpha Epsilon: Living Groups Annual Review Correspondence: General, 2001-2002 (Box 15)
  - Annual Reports: Sigma Chi: Living Groups Annual Review Correspondence: General, 2002-2007 (Box 15)
  - Annual Reports: Sigma Nu: Living Groups Annual Review Correspondence: General, 2002-2007 (Box 15)
  - Annual Reports: Sigma Phi Epsilon: Living Groups Annual Review Correspondence: General, 2003-2007 (Box 15)
  - Annual Reports: Theta Chi: Living Groups Annual Review Correspondence: General, 2002-2003 (Box 15)
  - Annual Reports: Wayne Manor: Living Groups Annual Review Correspondence: General, 2002-2003 (Box 15)
  - Annual Reports: Untitled AN: Unfoldered 93, 2001-2002 (Box 15)
  - Annual Reports: Untitled AN: Committee Annual Review Schedule, 2001-2002 (Box 15)
  - AFA Outstanding Change Initiative Award Nomination Materials, 2003 (Box 15)
  - Untitled 94, 1992-2007 (Box 15)
  - Composite Photographs: Sigma Nu, 1989-1998 (Box 16)
  - Composite Photographs: Alpha Epsilon Pi, 1992-1999 (Box 16)
  - Composite Photographs: Alpha Phi Omega, 1993-1994 (Box 16)
  - Composite Photographs: Chi Psi, 1993-1999 (Box 16)
  - Composite Photographs: Phi Kappa Sigma, 1988-1989 (Box 16)
  - Composite Photographs: Beta Theta Pi, 1990-1999 (Box 16)
  - Composite Photographs: Pi Kappa Alpha, 1994 (Box 16)
  - Composite Photographs: Theta Chi, 1992-1999 (Box 16)
  - Composite Photographs: Delta Kappa Epsilon, 1994-1999 (Box 16)
  - Composite Photographs: Sigma Chi, 1990-1999 (Box 16)
  - Composite Photographs: Delta Tau Delta, 1990-1994 (Box 16)
  - Composite Photographs: Zau Tau Alpha, 2007-2008 (Box 17)
  - Composite Photographs: Delta Sigma Phi, 1993-1999 (Box 17)
  - Composite Photographs: Kappa Sigma, 1989-1997 (Box 17)
  - Composite Photographs: Pi Kappa Phi, 1993-1997 (Box 17)
  - Composite Photographs: Sigma Alpha Epsilon, 1989-1999 (Box 17)
  - Composite Photographs: Phi Delta Theta, 1994-1999 (Box 17)
  - Composite Photographs: Kappa Alpha Order, 1993-2007 (Box 17)
  - Composite Photographs: Alpha Tau Omega, 1990-2006 (Box 17)
  - Composite Photographs: Phi Kappa Psi, 1992-1999 (Box 17)